[
  {
    "question": "Who was swallowed by Bigalink Michael Chungus?",
    "options": [
      "Ludwig",
      "Billy",
      "Roddir",
      "Alya",
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha",
      "Kaskus/Ayo"
    ],
    "answer": "Roddir"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you spell Ryan and Ethan's last name? (case-sensitive)",
    "answer": "Castel",
    "variants": ["Castiel", "Kastel", "Casstel", "Casstell"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has spoken directly to the most gods?",
    "options": [
      "Roddir",
      "Alya",
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha",
      "Kaskus/Ayo",
      "Ludwig",
      "Billy"
    ],
    "answer": "Billy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who killed the first humanoid enemy, in-session?",
    "options": [
      "Kaskus/Ayo",
      "Ludwig",
      "Billy",
      "Roddir",
      "Alya",
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha"
    ],
    "answer": "Sypha"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who landed the final blow on Silverwish?",
    "options": [
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha",
      "Kaskus/Ayo",
      "Ludwig",
      "Billy",
      "Roddir",
      "Alya"
    ],
    "answer": "Giggly"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you spell Del's full first name? (case-sensitive)",
    "answer": "Del'ayna",
    "variants": ["Del'Ayna", "Del'anya", "Del'Anya", "Delanya", "del'ayna"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who sent racoons to Rivercross, dooming it?",
    "options": [
      "Billy",
      "Roddir",
      "Alya",
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha",
      "Kaskus/Ayo",
      "Ludwig"
    ],
    "answer": "Alya"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you spell the name of the bugbear that has Elderwalker's notes? (case-sensitive)",
    "answer": "G'Hoth",
    "variants": ["Gahoth", "Ga'hoth", "Ghoth"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which member is actually a homeowner?",
    "options": [
      "Kaskus/Ayo",
      "Ludwig",
      "Billy",
      "Roddir",
      "Alya",
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha"
    ],
    "answer": "Ludwig"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who revived an invisible and dead party member during Arcane Night?",
    "options": [
      "Kaskus/Ayo",
      "Ludwig",
      "Billy",
      "Roddir",
      "Alya",
      "Giggly",
      "Sypha"
    ],
    "answer": "Kaskus/Ayo"
  }
]
